A Guide to the Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
The Library of Virginia
40167
45 cu. ft., 45 boxes
Virginia. Governor (Gilmore: 1998-2001)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Some material is restricted until 2015.
Acquisition Information
Transferred November 18, 2002, by James S. Gilmore.
Biographical/Historical Information
James Stuart Gilmore III was elected Virginia's 68th Governor in November 1997 and served in this capacity from January 1998 to January 2002. Jim Gilmore was born in Richmond, Virginia, on October 6, 1949. He graduated from the University of Virginia in 1971 with a degree in Foreign Policy and then joined the U.S. Army, where he then graduated with honors from the Army Intelligence School. He joined the 650th Military Intelligence Group and was stationed in West Germany. After his tour was completed, he entered law school at the University of Virginia and graduated in 1977. Jim Gilmore was elected in 1987 as Commonwealth's Attorney for Henrico County, was reelected in 1991 and was elected Virginia's Attorney General in 1993. He is married to the former Roxane Gatling of Suffolk.
Scope and Content
Contains records concerning legislation passed during the General Assembly session and sent to the Governor's Office for action. Records are arranged by General Assembly session and then by bill number. Folders for each bill typically contain a summary of the legislation, fiscal impact statement, accounting of General Assembly votes, and copies of the legislation. Additionally, each folder contains materials that are sealed per the transfer agreement until the year 2015. These sealed records include correspondence with and within the Governor's Policy Office, the Office of the Attorney General, notes, and drafts of documents related to the legislation.
Contents List
- 1998 Lists of Bills PasseD, Bills Amended by Governor, Vetoed by Governor (Box 1, Folder 1)
- SB 1 (98) T. George Vaughan, Jr., Memorial Highway (Box 1, Folder 2)
- SB 2 (98) Constitutional Amendment; Agreements for Sharing Revenues (Box 1, Folder 3)
- SB 3 (98) Constitutional Amendment; Disabled and Unfit Judges (Box 1, Folder 4)
- SB 5 (98) Property Tax Exemption; Good Shepherd Housing and Family Services, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- SB 9 (98) Special License Plates; Supporters of State Baseball Teams (Box 1, Folder 6)
- SB 11 (98) Payment of Certain Court Fees by Personal Check or Credit Card (Box 1, Folder 7)
- SB 13 (98) Congressional Districts (Box 1, Folder 8)
- SB 14 (98) Guardians and Conservators (Box 1, Folder 9)
- SB 15 (98) Senatorial Districts; Technical Adjustment in Henrico County (Box 1, Folder 10)
- SB 16 (98) Uninsured Employer's Fund; Payment of Tax (Box 1, Folder 11)
- SB 17 (98) Claims: Johnny Beth Moore (Box 1, Folder 12)
- SB 20 (98) VRS: Benefit Payments (Box 1, Folder 13)
- SB 22 (98) Economic Interest Disclosure Reports; Provisions (Box 1, Folder 14)
- SB 23 (98) Transient Occupancy Tax; Authorized in Wythe County (Box 1, Folder 15)
- SB 24 (98) Property Conveyance; National Guard Armory in Richlands (Box 1, Folder 16)
- SB 26 (98) Subdivision Streets (Box 1, Folder 17)
- SB 31 (98) Higher Educational Institutions Bond Act of 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- SB 32 (98) Portsmouth City Charter (Box 1, Folder 19)
- SB 33 (98) Emergency Medical Services Do Not Resuscitate Orders (Box 1, Folder 20)
- SB 34 (98) Homestead Exemption; Real Estate (Box 1, Folder 21)
- SB 36 (98) Bad Checks; Recovery of Costs in Localities (Box 1, Folder 22)
- SB 37 (98) Scottsville Town Charter (Box 1, Folder 23)
- SB 38 (98) VRS; Deferred Compensation Plan (Box 1, Folder 24)
- SB 39 (98) VRS; Compliance with Internal Revenue Code (Box 1, Folder 25)
- SB 40 (98) Insurance Companies; Declarations of Estimated Assessments (Box 1, Folder 26)
- SB 41 (98) Automobile Clubs (Box 1, Folder 27)
- SB 47 (98) Roll-back Taxes on Property in Land Use Taxation (Box 1, Folder 28)
- SB 52 (98) Chesapeake City Charter (Box 1, Folder 29)
- SB 53 (98) Chesapeake Hospital Authority (Box 1, Folder 30)
- SB 54 (98) Irrevocable Preneed Funeral Trusts (Box 1, Folder 31)
- SB 55 (98) Portsmouth Hotel and Conference Center; Sales Tax Revenue (Box 1, Folder 32)
- SB 56 (98) Craney Island; Construction of Additional Marine Terminal (Box 1, Folder 33)
- SB 58 (98) Insurance; Policy Forms Filed with SCC (Box 1, Folder 34)
- SB 59 (98) Transfer of Property from VRS to Science Museum (Box 1, Folder 35)
- SB 61 (98) Arlington County, Election of Board, Filling Vacancies (Box 1, Folder 36)
- SB 62 (98) Board of Zoning Appeals (Box 1, Folder 37)
- SB 64 (98) Property and Casualty Insurance Guaranty Association (Box 1, Folder 38)
- SB 65 (98) Member Contributions to VRS (Box 1, Folder 39)
- SB 67 (98) Public School Authority (Box 1, Folder 40)
- SB (72) Fredericksburg City Charter (Box 1, Folder 41)
- SB 81 (98) Sales Tax Exemption; Cecil D. Hylton Memorial Chapel Foundation (Box 1, Folder 42)
- SB 87 (98) Banking; Certificate of Authority (Box 1, Folder 43)
- SB 88 (98) Banking: Fees for Supervision, Regulation and Investigations (Box 1, Folder 44)
- SB 89 (98) Claims; Kenneth J. Settle, Sr. and Family (Box 1, Folder 45)
- SB 94 (98) Martial Arts Instruction; Regulation (Box 1, Folder 46)
- SB 95 (98) Mortgage Lenders and Brokers; Acquisition of Control (Box 1, Folder 47)
- SB 100 (98) Court Appearance of a Person Not Free on Bail (Box 1, Folder 48)
- SB 105 (98) Compromises on Behalf of Persons Under a Disability (Box 1, Folder 49)
- SB 106 (98) Appomattox River; Portion A Scenic River (Box 1, Folder 50)
- SB 107 (98) Parking in Augusta, Dinwiddie and Rockbridge Counties (Box 1, Folder 51)
- SB 108 (98) Special License Plates; 1999 Bicentennial of George Washington (Box 1, Folder 52)
- SB 109 (98) Tax Classifications of Farm Machinery (Box 1, Folder 53)
- SB 111 (98) Drakes Branch Charter (Box 1, Folder 54)
- SB 112 (98) Credit Unions; Electronic Filing of Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 55)
- SB 113 (98) BPOL Tax on Professional Employer Organization Firms (Box 1, Folder 56)
- SB 120 (98) Literacy Passport Tests (Box 1, Folder 57)
- SB 121 (98) Special License Plates; Loyal Order of Moose (Box 1, Folder 58)
- SB 125 (98) Defined Contribution Plan for State Employees in Exempted Positions (Box 1, Folder 59)
- SB 126 (98) Sickness and Disability Program for State Employees (Box 1, Folder 60)
- SB 143 (98) Martinsville City Charter (Box 1, Folder 61)
- SB 144 (98) Transient Occupancy Tax; Additional Tax for Certain Counties (Box 1, Folder 62)
- SB 152 (98) Electronic Filing of Information (Box 1, Folder 63)
- SB 153 (98) Trade and Commerce; Digital Signatures (Box 1, Folder 64)
- SB 156 (98) FOIA: Electronic Communications Meetings (Box 1, Folder 65)
- SB 157 (98) Professional Boxers and Wrestlers; Regulation (Box 1, Folder 66)
- SB 168 (98) Business and Education Partnerships (Box 1, Folder 67)
- SB 169 (98) Local Social Services Boards (Box 1, Folder 68)
- SB 170 (98) Funding for Deputy Sheriffs (Box 1, Folder 69)
- SB 172 (98) Health Insurance; Purchase by Surviving Spouse (Box 1, Folder 70)
- SB 173 (98) Health Insurance; Purchase by Surviving Spouse (Box 1, Folder 71)
- SB 174 (98) Instruction in History and Principles of State and US Flags (Box 1, Folder 72)
- SB 180 (98) Sentencing Guidelines (Box 1, Folder 73)
- SB 181 (98) Attorney Disciplinary Proceedings (Box 1, Folder 74)
- SB 185 (98) Juvenile Records (Box 1, Folder 75)
- SB 192 (98) Social Services Fraud Control Program (Box 1, Folder 76)
- SB 193 (98) Business Licenses; Workers' Compensation Coverage Board (Box 1, Folder 77)
- SB 195 (98) Public Building Authority; Refunding of Bonds Issued by Others (Box 1, Folder 78)
- SB 196 (98) Additional Jurors (Box 1, Folder 79)
- SB 199 (98) Offenses Involving Telecommunications Devices (Box 1, Folder 80)
- SB 205 (98) SOQ in Public Schools; Accreditation Requirements (Box 1, Folder 81)
- SB 206 (98) Family Life Education (Box 1, Folder 82)
- SB 208 (98) Criminal Procedures; DNA Analysis and Databank (Box 1, Folder 83)
- SB 218 (98) Property of Henrico County in the City of Richmond (Box 1, Folder 84)
- SB 222 (98) Murder; Animate Object Penetration is a Premeditated Crime (Box 1, Folder 85)
- SB 224 (98) Insurance; Private Review Agents (Box 1, Folder 86)
- SB 226 (98) Premarital Agreements (Box 2, Folder 1)
- SB 228 (98) State Recordation Tax (Box 2, Folder 2)
- SB 231 (98) Highway Construction by Counties (Box 3, Folder 3)
- SB 232 (98) Wine Licenses; Holders to Sell Boat Owners (Box 2, Folder 4)
- SB 234 (98) Recordation Tax (Box 2, Folder 5)
- SB 236 (98) State Park Projects (Box 2, Folder 6)
- SB 237 (98) Sheriffs; Monthly Report to Compensation Board (Box 2, Folder 7)
- SB 238 (98) Home/Electronic Incarceration; Jails Operated by Sheriffs (Box 2, Folder 8)
- SB 239 (98) Speed Limits; Increased on Access Highways with Divided Roadways (Box 2, Folder 9)
- SB 240 (98) Property Lease; Smiley Block Company Property (Box 2, Folder 10)
- SB 243 (98) Banking; Acquisitions of State Banks by Out-of-State Companies (Box 2, Folder 11)
- SB 245 (98) Health Care Plan for State Employees; Coverage for Diabetes (Box 2, Folder 12)
- SB 246 (98) State Employee's Grievance Procedure (Box 2, Folder 13)
- SB 247 (98) Insurance; Retaliatory Payments and Reports (Box 2, Folder 14)
- SB 248 (98) Insurance; Financial Regulation of Certain Insurers (Box 2, Folder 15)
- SB 249 (98) Lien for Water and Sewer Charges and Taxes; City of Fairfax (Box 2, Folder 16)
- SB 251 (98) Health Insurance; Coverage for Hemophilia (Box 2, Folder 17)
- SB 252 (98) University of Virginia; Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 18)
- SB 258 (98) Buses; Local Restriction on Operation (Box 2, Folder 19)
- SB 261 (98) Investment of Public Funds (Box 2, Folder 20)
- SB 262 (98) State Parks; Issuance of a Golden Passport Card (Box 2, Folder 21)
- SB 263 (98) Public Defender Offices in Patrick County (Box 2, Folder 22)
- SB 265 (98) Immunity for Ski Patrol Emergency Assistance (Box 2, Folder 23)
- SB 267 (98) Higher Education Tuition Trust Fund (Box 2, Folder 24)
- SB 270 (98) Notification Upon Identification of Hearing or Visual Impairment (Box 2, Folder 25)
- SB 273 (98) Group Homes for Aged, Infirm or Disabled Persons (Box 2, Folder 26)
- SB 275 (98) Concealed Weapons; Applicable to Retired Law Officers (Box 2, Folder 27)
- SB 276 (98) Small Claims Courts (Box 2, Folder 28)
- SB 281 (98) Consumer Real Estate Settlement Protection Act (Box 2, Folder 29)
- SB 282 (98) Income Tax; Contribution to Historic Resources Fund (Box 2, Folder 30)
- SB 284 (98) Reciprocal Agreements for Nonresident Income Tax Liability (Box 2, Folder 31)
- SB 285 (98) Miller School of Albemarle; Board of Trustees (Box 2, Folder 32)
- SB 286 (98) Horse Industry Board; Alternate Members (Box 2, Folder 33)
- SB 288 (98) VCCS; Reduced Tuition for Certain Students (Box 2, Folder 34)
- SB 289 (98) Child Support Enforcement; Privatization (Box 2, Folder 35)
- SB 290 (98) State Park Planning (Box 2, Folder 36)
- SB 291 (98) Criminal Background Checks (Box 2, Folder 37)
- SB 293 (98) Child Support (Box 2, Folder 38)
- SB 295 (98) Public Utility Service; Refund or Credit for Excessive Charges (Box 2, Folder 39)
- SB 299 (98) ABC; First Offender Under Age 21 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- SB 300 (98) Driver's License; Suspended for Failure to Pay Fines (Box 2, Folder 41)
- SB 301 (98) Special License Plates; 250th Anniversary of City of Alexandria (Box 2, Folder 42)
- SB 302 (98) Freya Dalton Bridge (Box 2, Folder 43)
- SB 306 (98) Community Service Boards; Employee Background Check (Box 2, Folder 44)
- SB 308 (98) Ordinances Prohibiting Parking in Streets and Highways (Box 2, Folder 45)
- SB 309 (98) Board of Zoning Appeals (Box 2, Folder 46)
- SB 310 (98) Vehicle Registrations (Box 2, Folder 47)
- SB 313 (98) Consumer Finance Companies; Examination and Accounts, Books, etc. (Box 2, Folder 48)
- SB 315 (98) Traffic Signals; Photo-Enforcement (Box 2, Folder 49)
- SB 316 (98) Petition Requirements in Presidential Elections (Box 2, Folder 50)
- SB 319 (98) Drug Assessment of Certain Offenders (Box 2, Folder 51)
- SB 318 (98) Charter Schools (Box 2, Folder 52)
- SB 319 (98) Dept. of General Services; Surplus Property (Box 2, Folder 53)
- SB 321 (98) Corporate Trustees; Substitution (Box 2, Folder 54)
- SB 322 (98) Constitutional Amendment Debt of Local Governments (Box 2, Folder 55)
- SB 324 (98) Statute of Limitations of Prosecutions (Box 2, Folder 56)
- SB 327 (98) Service of Garnishments on Corporations (Box 2, Folder 57)
- SB 328 (98) Smith Mountain Lake; No-Discharge Zone for Boat Sewage (Box 2, Folder 58)
- SB 330 (98) Small Investor-Owned Telephone Utilities (Box 2, Folder 59)
- SB 335 (98) Chesapeake Bay Bridge and Tunnel Connections (Box 2, Folder 60)
- SB 336 (98) Motor Vehicle Dealers (Box 2, Folder 61)
- SB 338 (98) Uniform Statewide Building Code; Penalty for Violations (Box 2, Folder 62)
- SB 340 (98) Capital Region Airport Commission (Box 2, Folder 63)
- SB 341 (98) Education Assistance Authority; Education Loan Authority (Box 2, Folder 64)
- SB 343 (98) Docking Judgments; Name Change of Donor (Box 2, Folder 65)
- SB 344 (98) Vehicle Window-Tinting Films (Box 2, Folder 66)
- SB 346 (98) Roanoke Higher Education Authority; Membership (Box 2, Folder 67)
- SB 351 (98) Dog and Cat Licenses (Box 2, Folder 68)
- SB 352 (98) School Board Salaries; Various Counties and Cities (Box 2, Folder 69)
- SB 354 (98) Local Penalty Powers in Chesapeake Bay Preservation Areas (Box 2, Folder 70)
- SB 357 (98) Sentencing Guidelines; Worksheets (Box 2, Folder 71)
- SB 358 (98) Elections; Duties and Powers of General Registrars, Pollbooks (Box 2, Folder 72)
- SB 362 (98) Suspension and Expulsion of Students (Box 2, Folder 73)
- SB 363 (98) Study; Unemployment Trust Fund Commission, Created (Box 2, Folder 74)
- SB 364 (98) Access to Juvenile Records (Box 2, Folder 74)
- SB 365 (98) Workers' Comp.; Duty to Furnish Medical Attention (Box 2, Folder 76)
- SB 367 (98) Authority to Cut Grass; Augusta, Henry and Rockingham Counties (Box 2, Folder 77)
- SB 369 (98) Megan's Law; Community Notification (Box 2, Folder 78)
- SB 372 (98) Genetic Information (Box 2, Folder 79)
- SB 373 (98) Officers of Election; Hours of Service (Box 2, Folder 80)
- SB 378 (98) Postmortem Examinations (Box 2, Folder 81)
- SB 379 (98) High Voltage Electric Transmission Lines (Box 2, Folder 81)
- SB 381 (98) Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (Box 2, Folder 83)
- SB 382 (98) Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (Box 2, Folder 84)
- SB 383 (98) Workforce Training Council (Box 2, Folder 85)
- SB 384 (98) Workforce Training at Community Colleges (Box 2, Folder 86)
- SB 385 (98) Landlord and Tenant; Who May Recover Rent or Possession (Box 2, Folder 87)
- SB 388 (98) Foster Care; Adoption; Termination of Parental Rights (Box 2, Folder 88)
- SB 391 (98) Planning and Budgeting Procedures (Box 2, Folder 89)
- SB 394 (98) Public Guardians and Conservators (Box 2, Folder 90)
- SB 397 (98) Schools for the Deaf and Blind (Box 2, Folder 91)
- SB 401 (98) Impact Statements for Proposed Legislation (Box 2, Folder 92)
- SB 402 (98) Assistive Technology Device Warranties Act (Box 2, Folder 93)
- SB 409 (98) Special license Plates; Supporters of Nat. Air and Space Museum (Box 2, Folder 94)
- SB 410 (98) Disabled Parking Fines; Prepayment (Box 2, Folder 95)
- SB 411 (98) Lease of Mason Neck State Park (Box 3, Folder 1)
- SB 414 (98) Attorney-Physician Communications (Box 3, Folder 2)
- SB 415 (98) Community Service Boards; Prescreening (Box 3, Folder 3)
- SB 416 (98) Board of Social Services; Members (Box 3, Folder 4)
- SB 417 (98) Child Care (Box 3, Folder 5)
- SB 419 (98) Child Welfare Agencies (Box 3, Folder 6)
- SB 420 (98) Definition of Family Day Homes (Box 3, Folder 7)
- SB 421 (98) Insurance Fraud; Delegation of Duties to Department of State Police (Box 3, Folder 8)
- SB 422 (98) Insurance Agents; Continuing Education Requirements (Box 3, Folder 9)
- SB 423 (98) Insurance; Motor Vehicle Rental Contract Insurance (Box 3, Folder 10)
- SB 425 (98) Opening of the School Year (Box 3, Folder 11)
- SB 426 (98) Threats (Box 3, Folder 12)
- SB 429 (98) Emergency Medical Services Orders (Box 3, Folder 13)
- SB 431 (98) Physical Examiners of School Bus Drivers (Box 3, Folder 14)
- SB 433 (98) Children's Medical Security Plan (Box 3, Folder 15)
- SB 435 (98) Amber Warning Lights; Funeral Processions (Box 3, Folder 16)
- SB 437 (98) Motorcycle Helmets (Box 3, Folder 17)
- SB 438 (98) Uniform Statewide Building Code; Adult Homes (Box 3, Folder 18)
- SB 440 (98) Legislation Relating to Debt (Box 3, Folder 19)
- SB 442 (98) Shipyard Incentive Commission (Box 3, Folder 20)
- SB 443 (98) Workers' Compensation; Voluntary Payments (Box 3, Folder 21)
- SB 445 (98) Public Procurement Act; Exemp. To Jamestown - Yorktown Fund (Box 3, Folder 22)
- SB 447 (98) Controlled Subsidiary; Transaction of Insurance (Box 3, Folder 23)
- SB 449 (98) Hampton Roads Sanitation District Commission (Box 3, Folder 24)
- SB 451 (98) Williamsburg School Board Terms (Box 3, Folder 25)
- SB 452 (98) Charitable Gaming Commission; Use of Proceeds, Audit Fees (Box 3, Folder 26)
- SB 454 (98) Design-Build/Construction Management Review Board (Box 3, Folder 27)
- SB 457 (98) Restricted Driver's Licenses (Box 3, Folder 28)
- SB 458 (98) Boating While Under the Influence (Box 3, Folder 29)
- SB 462 (98) Uniform Consultation Referral Form (Box 3, Folder 30)
- SB 463 (98) Department for the Aging (Box 3, Folder 31)
- SB 464 (98) Secretary of Health and Human Resources; Duties (Box 3, Folder 32)
- SB 465 (98) Department for the Aging; Advisory Board (Box 3, Folder 33)
- SB 466 (98) COPN: Nursing Home Beds (Box 3, Folder 34)
- SB 467 (98) Fire Programs Fund (Box 3, Folder 35)
- SB 469 (98) Public Procurement Act; Chesapeake Hospital Authority (Box 3, Folder 36)
- SB 470 (98) Preneed Funeral Contracts (Box 3, Folder 37)
- SB 475 (98) Income Tax; Withholding Statements (Box 3, Folder 38)
- SB 476 (98) Capital Expenditure Special Fund (Box 3, Folder 39)
- SB 478 (98) Donations of Food to Charitable Organizations by Businesses (Box 3, Folder 40)
- SB 480 (98) Placement of Amateur Radio Antennas (Box 3, Folder 41)
- SB 481 (98) Child Support; Retroactivity (Box 3)
- SB 482 (98) Admissions Tax in Nelson County (Box 3, Folder 43)
- SB 483 (98) Oil Release Report and Notifications (Box 3, Folder 44)
- SB 484 (98) License Reinstatement Fee; Neurotrauma Fund (Box 3, Folder 45)
- SB 487 (98) Powers of Resources Authority (Box 3, Folder 46)
- SB 488 (98) Certificates Authorizing of Law (Box 3, Folder 47)
- SB 490 (98) Accident Reports; Photographs (Box 3, Folder 48)
- SB 494 (98) Joint Commission Behavioral Health Care (Box 3, Folder 49)
- SB 495 (98) Membership of MHMRSAS Board (Box 3, Folder 50)
- SB 498 (98) Adult Protective Services (Box 3, Folder 51)
- SB500 (98) Elections; Form of Ballots (Box 3, Folder 52)
- SB 501 (98) Community Service Boards (Box 3, Folder 53)
- SB 503 (98) State Correctional Facilities; Religious Services (Box 3, Folder 54)
- SB 510 (98) Asbestos and Lead Contractors, Workers, and Supervisors (Box 3, Folder 55)
- SB 512 (98) Solicitation of Contributions; Exemptions (Box 3, Folder 56)
- SB 514 (98) Relocation of Utilities (Box 3, Folder 57)
- SB 516 (98) Health Regulatory Boards; Inactive Licensure (Box 3, Folder 58)
- SB 523 (98) Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (Box 3, Folder 59)
- SB 527 (98) Standards of Quality; Basic Skills, Programs, etc. (Box 3, Folder 60)
- SB 537 (98) Certain Town Elections; Postponement and Rescheduling (Box 3, Folder 61)
- SB 540 (98) Civil Cases; Exclusive Jurisdiction of General District Court (Box 3, Folder 62)
- SB 542 (98) Gaming Contracts (Box 3, Folder 63)
- SB 543 (98) Period for Filing for Amended State Tax Returns (Box 3, Folder 64)
- SB 548 (98) Statewide Cancer Registry (Box 3, Folder 65)
- SB 549 (98) Board of Medicine; Chronic Pain Guidelines (Box 3, Folder 66)
- SB 550 (98) Health Professions; Physical Therapist (Box 3, Folder 67)
- SB 551 (98) Statewide Prehospital and Interhospital Trauma Triage Plan (Box 3, Folder 68)
- SB 553 (98) Health Insurance; Calculation of Cost-Sharing Provisions (Box 3, Folder 69)
- SB 554 (98) Settlement Agents (Box 3, Folder 70)
- SB 557 (98) Child Protective Services; Infant Dependent on Controlled Subs. (Box 3, Folder 71)
- SB 558 (98) Reading Incentive Grants program and Fund (Box 3, Folder 72)
- SB 560 (98) Practice of Pharmacy; Penalties (Box 3, Folder 73)
- SB 562 (98) State Aid to Mass Transit (Box 3, Folder 74)
- SB 563 (98) Commission on Equity in Public Education (Box 3, Folder 75)
- SB 566 (98) Bonds for Northern Virginia Transportation Program (Box 3, Folder 76)
- SB 567 (98) Transportation Contract Revenue Bond Act (Box 3, Folder 77)
- SB 568 (98) Special License Plates; Supporters of Credit Union (Box 3, Folder 78)
- SB 570 (98) Vested Rights (Box 3, Folder 79)
- SB 577 (98) Public Rights-of-Way; Relocating Telecommunications Facilities (Box 3, Folder 80)
- SB 578 (98) Open Video Systems (Box 3, Folder 81)
- SB 579 (98) Traffic Safety Fund (Box 3, Folder 82)
- SB 585 (98) Hearing Impairment Identification and Monitoring System (Box 3, Folder 83)
- SB 588 (98) Photo-Enforcement of Toll Payments (Box 3, Folder 84)
- SB 590 (98) Condominium Act; Limitation on Occupancy (Box 3, Folder 85)
- SB 591 (98) Hearing Impairment Identification and Monitoring System (Box 4, Folder 1)
- SB 595 (98) Study: Abolition of Child Day-Care Council (Box 4, Folder 2)
- SB 598 (98) Rappahannock River Basin Commission (Box 4, Folder 3)
- SB 599 (98) Occupational Therapists (Box 4, Folder 4)
- SB 601 (98) Medical Assistance Services; Children and Young Adults Special Needs (Box 4, Folder 5)
- SB 603 (98) Certificates of Public Need (Box 4, Folder 6)
- SB 604 (98) Number of Deputies (Box 4, Folder 7)
- SB 606 (98) Investment of University of Virginia Endowment Funds (Box 4, Folder 8)
- SB 607 (98) Economic Development Partnership Authority (Box 4, Folder 9)
- SB 608 (98) Mental Health; Involuntary Temporary Detention (Box 4, Folder 10)
- SB 614 (98) Community Policing Programs (Box 4, Folder 11)
- SB 615 (98) Cultural Diversity Training for Law-Enforcement Officers (Box 4, Folder 12)
- SB 616 (98) Regional Cooperation Act (Box 4, Folder 13)
- SB 624 (98) Commercial Vehicles on Interstate Highways (Box 4, Folder 14)
- SB 625 (98) Funds from Telephone Service or Credit Cards (Box 4, Folder 16)
- SB 626 (98) Medical Assistance Services; Pre-PACE and PACE Plans (Box 4, Folder 17)
- SB 628 (98) Civil Immunity; Emergency Care to Animals (Box 4, Folder 18)
- SB 630 (98) Do Not Resuscitate Orders (Box 4, Folder 19)
- SB 631 (98) Concealed Handgun Permits (Box 4, Folder 20)
- SB 632 (98) Prescription Dispensing Record Disclosure (Box 4, Folder 21)
- SB 633 (98) Clean Fuel Fleet Program (Box 4, Folder 22)
- SB 635 (98) Motor Vehicle Warranty Enforcement Act: Leased Vehicles (Box 4, Folder 23)
- SB 640 (98) Property Owners' Assoc.; Amendment of Declaration (Box 4, Folder 24)
- SB 641 (98) Condemnation; Bona Fide Effort to Purchase (Box 4, Folder 25)
- SB 642 (98) Judge Suspension (Box 4, Folder 26)
- SB 645 (98) Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission (Box 4, Folder 27)
- SB 648 (98) Prisoner Litigation Reform (Box 4, Folder 28)
- SB 651 (98) Roanoke Higher Education Center Authority (Box 4, Folder 29)
- SB 657 (98) Regulation of Water Transport of Wastes (Box 4, Folder 29)
- SB 660 (98) Practitioner Information (Box 4, Folder 32)
- SB 661 (98) Confined Animal Feeding Operations (Box 4, Folder 33)
- SB 664 (98) Attorney General Power to Prosecute Environmental Crimes (Box 4, Folder 34)
- SB 665 (98) Respiratory Care Practitioners (Box 4, Folder 35)
- SB 667 (98) Readmission of Suspended and Expelled Students to Public Schools (Box 4, Folder 36)
- SB 672 (98) Literary Fund (Box 4, Folder 37)